Don't touch me with your right hand!
This is the last grenade I have on me.
Thinking of it as Nice, I will let it explode gently.
If they oppose you, kill them.
Ennis, you have to be joking, right?!
Ennis!
What?!
I don't know about the guy, but the woman looks to be all right.
男のほうは分からないが
女のほうは無事だな
I thought he was just plain scum, but he turned out to be quite amazing.
あいつ ただのクズかと思ったら
大したもんだ
そう思ゎないか?
Don't you agree?
Well then, the deal was that I would kill the one left alive,
さてと…
生き残ったほうを
俺が殺す約束だつたが…
あいつの生死が不明になつた
どうすればいいと思う?
but we don't know whether or not he's still alive.
What should we do?
Is that guy Huey your lover?
ヒ丑一イつて奴は
お別の恋人か?
家族か ?
Family?
Your father?
父親か ?
不老不死つてのは本当なのか ?
Is he really immortal?
Can it be that...
ひよっとして あれか?
you're thinking that I may threaten Huey and take the secret of immortality?
俺ヵヾヒユ一イを脅して
不老不死の秘密を
横取りするかもしれない…
とか者えてるのか?
Is he your only family?
お前の家族は そいつだけか ?
Because he is your only family, you want to protect him no matter what, I see.
そいつカヾ ただ ー 人の家族だから
何としても守りたいつてゎけだ
そうだろ ?
Right?
ーつ者えたんだけどな…
I just thought of something...
If you and I marry, I will become Huey's son.
俺とお前が結婚すれば
俺はそのヒユ一イつて奴の息子になる
Then I will be your family as well, so the problem will have disappeared.
そうすると俺も お前たちの
家族ってことになるから
問題はなくなるゎけだ
You can think of it as a joke if you will,
冗談と思うのは勝手だが
俺は本気だ
but I'm serious.
Unlike your "friends," I won't betray you.
俺は お前の仲間と違って
お前を裏切らない
ヒユ一イから不死身の秘密を
奪うようなマネもしない
I won't try to obtain the secret of immortality from Huey either,
because I don't need something like that.
そんなものは必要ないからな
なぜなら俺は
不死の力があろうが なかろうカヾ
Knowing that whether I am immortal or not, I won't die no matter what...
絶対に死な蔓いからだ
俺ヵヾ そう信じているからだ
That's what I believe,
だからお前も黙つて俺を信じろ
so keep silent and just believe me.
俺が決して死なない男だとm
I am a guy who will never die.
We will get to a river soon.
もうすぐ川に出る…
If you don't want to get caught by the police, jump off there.
警察に捕まる気がないなら
そこから飛ひ降りろ
Carve your answer to my request into the roof over there.
俺への答えは そこの屋根に
刻んでおいてくれ
じやあな
See you.
If you want to, you can throw your knife at me. I'll dodge it anyway.
投げたければ
ナイフを投げつけてもいいぞ
よけるから
ジヤグジ一は 普段は泣き虫だけど
Jacuzzi is normally a crybaby, but when he's made up his mind, he won't cry for sure.
覚悟を決めた時は
絶対に泣かないんですよ
あの錨曹を入れた時も
一度も泣き言を言ゎなかつたんです
He didn't spill one tear when he got that tattoo either.
Why is he always crying so much, then?
じやあ… いつもは何であんなに
泣き虫なんスか?
さて 覚悟はいいか? 刺青男
Well now, have you prepared yourself, tattoo guy?
くつ つつつ…
うゎあああああああ !
Have you gone crazy, boy?!
血迷つ たか 小僧~~ !
What?!
何!?
む? どうした? ハツ!
Why doesn't it work?!
バ力な!
No way!
I came up with this.
僕 思つたんだ…
きつと泣きたい時が
That the times when you want to cry are when you have to try your hardest.
一番 頑張らなきゃ
いけない時なんじゃないかつて…
That's why I've decided to cry in general.
だからね 普段から
たくさん泣いておくことにしたんだ
ノジヤクジ一丿
一番 泣き庭C )畦ノご流實涙き
会のうちノご蒐レごおくん右
Then, I will have shed all my tears when the time comes that I really want to cry,
一番 頑蒻らなきゃ蝿ノプな蝿畦に
も う涙が ヵW ご乙 'るようノご
so that my tears will have run dry when I really want to cry.
I'm leaving the rest to you.
あとは お願いします!
ぁね
姐さん!
Sis!
You jump down and meet up with the recovery crew.
二ツクは先に降りて
回収組と合流して下さい
便利だろう ?
Nifty, don't you think?
This thing fires bullets when you press it against someone and then clench your fist.
拳を握つて相手に押しつければ
弾が発射されるって仕組みだ
さて‥
とんだアクシデン卜だつたが
Well then, this was quite the accident,
この距離なら 貢様ー 人
丸焼きにするには十分だ…
but from this distance I should be able to burn you whole.
言い残すことはないか ボウズ!?
Any last words, boy?
What?!
何だ? 何だ この化け物は!?
What is this monster?!
まさか… レイル卜レ一サ一 ?
Could it be...
Rail Tracer?!
ノ丿丿ノツノツ丿ツ丿ツ丿ツ丿ツ丿ツ!
ハツハツハツハツハ
アイザックさん 三リアさん
Mr. Isaac, Ms. Miria.
なあに?
W-What?
I'm sorry. Thanks, I'm glad I got to talk with you in the end.
ごめんなさい… ありがとう
最後に2人と話せて
本当に良かつた…
ホツ‥
もしもー つだけ
私の ワガママを聞いてくれるなら…
Could you please listen to this request of mine?
私のこと 忘れないで下さい
Please, don't forget me.
Damn it!
クソツ ! 来るな! 来るナー
来るな ! クソ~ ! d '
This trash, this trash!
Damn it!
Die! Die! Die!
死ね! 死ね! 死ね!
Burn! Burn! Burn!
燃えろ! 燃えろ! 燃えろおお !
Bu—
燃え… ん?
Lまぁ‥
チ工ス君 !
Czes-kun!
Are you all right, Czes-kun?!
大丈夫か チ工ス君
しつかり して !
Straighten up!
何で…
Why?
Why won't you eat me?
何で… 私を食ベない…
Sis...
姐さん…
バ力め… 丸腰で何をする気だ!?
The idiot...
What are you planning to do without any weapons?
There is a gun within my heart!
銃は心の…
中にある !
何だ? さつきから… 敵か?
What's going on?!
It's been noisy... Is it an enemy?
うゎ~! アイザツクう !
Ohhh! Isaac!
うゎああ 何だ? こいつらは!
What's this?!
T-This must be Rail Tracer!
き きつとこれが
レイ丿し卜レ一サ一だよ!
It must have come to eat what it left of Czes-kun!
食ベ残しのチェス君を
食ベに来たんだよ!
クソ一 そんなことさせるか!
Damnit! We won't let it!
うつ うう
シヤグシ一!
Jacuzzi!
二一ス
Nice...
良かった
無事だったんだね
I'm glad you're all right.
I'm fine.
私は大丈夫
それより早く血を止めないと…
We have to stop your bleeding fast!
ああ これなんだね
例の新型爆弾…
So that was your newly developed bomb?
We did it. We got our hands on the treasure as well.
やつたね…
お宝も手に入れだんだ 僕だち
Jacuzzi?
ジヤグジ一?
Well, Nice...
あのね 二一ス…
僕はさ 今までちよっと
多く泣きすきたのかもしれない
I might have cried a little too much up till now,
so I've decided that the amount I cried counts towards you as well.
だからさ
多く泣きすきた分は
君の分まで泣いたつてことにするよ…
I've cried your part as well now,
僕が二一スの分も泣いだんだから
so even if bad things should happen from now on, don't cry.
これから つらいことがあっても
泣かないでよ
あっ… ジヤグジ一?
Jacuzzi?!
I thought this would happen sooner or later.
そろそろだとは思っていた…
お前の前にも何体か造つ だが
The ones I created before you betrayed me as well as soon as they got some unnecessary knowledge!
やはり余計な知識を得た途端に
裏切つたからな
I won't kill you fast.
ひと思いには殺さん…
たつぷりと苦しませてやる
I will make you suffer hard and—
ぐぁ ぐはつ !
工イツ ! 工イツ !
What did you do to Ennis?!
こいつ! 工二スに何したぁ?
何しだんだよお !
What did you do?!
貢様ら !
You!
I'd like to know as well!
そいつは俺も聞きてえなあ
う あなた!ま
You are...
イテ工じやねえか クソバ力野郎
That hurt, you asshole!
You guys!
みんな?
Hey Maiza, why didn't we die?
なあ マイ ザ一
何で俺たち死なねえんだ?
I see now!
そうか 貢様らが !
You bastards! You bastards drank it, didn't you?!
貴様らが飲んだんだな !
俺たち手袋や倉庫を
燃やしたことはあったけどよお
We have burned gloves and a storehouse before, but...
This is the first time we've put a head on fire!
頭を燃やすのは初めてだな
ぐおお はあ おおおおっ !
その男の頭に
右手をのせて下さい!
Please put your right hand on top of his head.
え? 右手?
Right hand?
早く!
Fast!
Ennis! You!
工二ス 貢様ああ一つ!?
You're in the way!
邪魔だあっ !
うおぁ…
食ベたいつて心に念じて !
Think that you want to eat him from your heart...
工二
Enni—
ぐぁ‥ カヾ Lま‥ あ‥
あれえ ? 赤いのがいなくなつてる
Huh? The red stuff has disappeared.
Ehh? How's Czes-kun?
え? チ工ス君は?
シヤグシ一… 今の…
Jacuzzi, what was that?
Rail Tracer, maybe?
レイ丿し卜レ一サ一‥ ヵな
ぬわ? ジャグジ一
Ah! Jacuzzi!
Donny!
ド二一 !
{チ工ス丿
さあ… 何き迷フごる
What are you hesitating for?
If I only stretch out my right hand a little further...
あと少レ
ほんの少レ右ソプ右手をノ申ばせば燗
良かつだぁ ! 本当に良かつだあ !
I'm so glad!
Really so glad!
Really!
本当にね~ でも どうしてケガが
治つちゃつたのかなァ?
But, I wonder how his wounds healed so fast?
That's easy to explain, Miria!
そんなのは簡単さ ミ リァ
いいか?
Listen carefully!
Rail Tracer eats bad children, right?
レイ丿し卜レ一サ一ってのは
悪い子からパクッて食べちゃうだろぉ?
Rail Tracer must have realized after eating Czes-kun that he was actually a good kid,
きっと食ったあとで
チ工スはいい子だつてことに
気力ヾついて 食ったものを
返しに来たのさぁ !
so he came back to return the parts he had eaten!
I see!
そつか!
それなら つじつまが合うね!
That makes sense!
違うよ…
You're wrong.
I'm nothing like a good child.
僕は いい子なんかじゃないよ
僕 ウソをついたんだ
I lied to you.
ウソ?
Lied?
I told you I was going to New York to meet my family,
二ユ一ヨ一クへ
家族に会いに行くって言ったけど…
ホン卜は… 知り合いに
会いに行くだけなんだ…
but I'm actually going there to meet an acquaintance.
僕には 家族なんていないんだ…
今までも… これからも
I don't have any family.
Until now... And from now—
そうだつたのかぁ !
Is that true?!
You're a good child after all, Czes-kun!
チェス君は やっぱり
いい子だったんだね!
みんなを心配させないように
そんなウソをついてたなんて
In order not to worry anyone, you told such a lie...
even though you're in the most pain of us all!
一番つらいのは
チェス君自身なのにな!
You are an extremely good kid!
チェス君は
すごく いい子だったんだね!
Umm, excuse me?
あ あの‥
Okay! You can count on me!
よし!
このアイザックに任しとけ一一いやぁ !
It's going to be all right now that you can leave it to Isaac,
よかつたね! チェス君
アイ ザックに任せれば もう安心だよ!
so it's all right to laugh now.
だからね もう笑つてもいいんだよ
Hey! Mr. Isaac, Ms. Miria!
お一一い アイザックさ一ん
三リアさ一ん
Czes-kun!
チ工スく一ん
I have a request.
お願いがあります…
It looks like I'm about to die, so...
私… もう死んでしまう
みたいなんですけど…
私のことも食ベてくれませんか?
could you please eat me as well?
Don't say such crazy things...
何バ力なこと言つてんだ
ああ‥ まだ‥
There's still a lot I want to tell Isaac and Miria.
アイ ザックさんたちに
言いたいことがたくさんあるんです…
So, please...
だから お願いです…
私を食ベて私の伝言を伝えて下さい
Eat me and relay my message to them.
言いたいことがあるんなら
自分で伝えろよ
You can tell them what you want yourself.
はつ あ
It's quite mysterious...
不思議だな
君を助ける方法を俺は知つてる
I knew how to save you.
そうか~
I see!
セラ一ドの知識は
もうすベてあなたに…
You have all of Szilard's knowledge now...
It was worth it to eat that old man.
あんなジジイを
食ベたかいがあったよ
My name is Firo. What about you?
俺の名前はフ イ一ロ 君は ?
Ennis... Why do you ask?
工二ス
どうして?
もう知つてるはずなのに
You ought to know already.
ふ 君のロから聞きだかつたのさ
I wanted to hear it from your mouth.
ヒユ一ヒユ一
What are you guys laughing about?
もぅ 何笑つてんですか !
ヒユ一ヒユ一
Mr. Isaac, and even Ms. Miria?!
アイザックさん 三リアさんまで
So, can you tell me where Dallas Genoard is?
話してもらおうか
ダラスジ工ノア一ドの行方を…
Are you awake?
お目覚めですか?
What's going on?!
何だ こりや?
お おめえら 何で生きてんだよ!
Why are you guys alive?!
Well... According to Firo, we have become immortal, like you.
さあ フイ一ロの話じや
あなた方と同じ
不死の体なのだそうです
ただし 残念ながら あなた方と違つて
老いて死ぬことはないそうですが
However, unlike you, we won't die of old age.
As such, we decided to let you take responsibility for your deeds.
そういうねけで あなた方には
ご自分たちのしたことの責任を
取つて頂こうと思います
Hey, hey, hey!
半永久的にハドソン川の底で
稟れ続けて頂きます
We will have you drown at the bottom of the Hudson River for about half a century.
We'd love to kill you here and now, but since you'll neither die to bullets nor fists, we don't really have a choice.
ひと思いにやつてやり たかつたが
撃つても殴つても
死なないんじゃ仕方ねえよな
ヌへツへツへツ キ一兄は優しいなあ
Keith is such a kind fellow.
あなた方が川の底で
老衰死するまで
He said that you guys would probably be bored at the bottom of the river,
暇だろうからって
墨別つてやつですね
せんベつ
so I guess you can call this a farewell gift.
That's horrible.
ひどい… ひどいゎ
That's so horrible!
I can say the same about them...
お言葉を返すようですが
Your brother killed some of my friends in a horrible way,
あなたのお兄さんは
我々の仲間を無残に殺したんです
a year ago, right here.
ー年前 この場所で…
しだがつて お譚ぴはしません
So, I won't apologize.
However, I have sympathy for the pain you feel.
ただ… あなたには心から
お悔やみ申し上げます
That is all we can do for you.
我々にできるのは それだけです
ハドソン川か…
The Hudson River?
捨てだのなら拾うのは勝手だな
If you threw them away, I assume we're free to pick them up?
ですヵヾ 所有権は
まずは肉親にあるのでは?
Don't the property rights belong to his family, though?
What are you planning to do to my brother?
兄を どうするおっも り ですか ?
We plan to examine him very thoroughly at some research center.
調ベる ある研究所で徹底的にな
兄を引き揚げて
頂けるんですか?
Will you salvage him, then?
Yes... I suppose he will be saved from the cruelty of eternal drowning.
永遠に溺れ続ける苦しみからは
解放してあげられるだろう
会ゎせては頂けるんですね ?
Will you let me meet him?!
約束しよう
I promise.
兄をお願いします
Please take good care of him.
イブちゃん! いいの?
Eve-chan! Are you okay with that?!
He's the man responsible for killing your family!
その人は君の家族の
趣き!こあたる人なんだよ!
言い訳に聞こえるなら
それでも構わん
If this is going to sound like an excuse, that's fine.
However, the murders of Raymond and Geoffrey weren't ordered by me.
だ力ヾレイモンドとジェフリ一を
殺したのは私の指示ではない
This man did that all of his own accord.
この男が勝手にしだことなのだ
ボス‥
Boss!
Is that you, boss?!
ボスじゃないですか…
私を助けに来てくれたぁ…
Did you come to save—
Did that help to show my sincerity?
これで少しは
示しカヾつけられたかな?
兄に 教えてあげたいんです
奇跡はあるって
I want to tell my brother...
that there are miracles.
If you save him from that watery hell,
川底の地獄から
救い出してあげれば
I think my brother will understand as well.
兄
も免力ると思つんです
邪魔しだな ガン ド一ル
Sorry for disturbing you, Gandors...
イブちやん!
Eve-chan!
おお!
工二スにフイ一ロにマイザ一!
Ennis, Firo, and Maiza!
It's been a long time, my good people!
久しぶりだな マイ いい人たち!
元気そうで何よ り だね
I'm glad you're all healthy!
そうそう 工二ス!
この子 チェス君っていうの!
Oh, Ennis! This boy's name is Czes-kun!
That's right, Ennis!
そうなんだよ 工二ス!
この子 工二スの弟にしろよ!
Let's make this boy into your little brother!
That'd be perfect!
それがいいよ !
これが俺たちのお…
お土産だ~い!
This is our... souvenir!
We kept him apart for you!
とつておきだね !
こんにちは
Hello there.
こんにちは…
Hello.
チ工ス
Czes.
マイザ一…
Maiza...
I came to this city to devour this man.
ノチ工ス丿
私な この男き貪らう潅め仁
この街ノごゃっごき盧ん右…
2人は知り合いってことなのか?
ミリア
Does this mean these two know each other, Miria?
That must be it, Isaac.
きつとそうだよ アイザツク
Czes-kun did say that he was coming here to meet someone.
知り合いに会いに来たつて
チェス君 言つてたし
stare
じ一一つ
{チ工ス丿 来だぞ…
The time has come.
そうレご私の亘享ノご右手そのせご
私き貪おうと實るんだ
He will now place his right hand on top of my head and will try to eat me.
Eat him before that! Now!
その蔚ノご貪 っ ごレまえ
さぁ 右手き マイザ一ノご突き出すん右 ノ
Stretch your right hand out to Maiza!
何きレごる ゴマ力シだ
What are you doing?!
He's fooling you!
気き便フごる振りきレご
A scheme in which he pretends to care, and afterwards, he will slowly devour me!
ぁご誓ゆフくり貪おうフご
魂胆なんだ…
いいんですよ チ工ス
It's all right, Czes.
Don't let him fool you!
ノチ工ス丿
左まさカるな…
It's all right...
いいんですよ 昔のままで…
Just like things used to be.
This guy is just like the rest...
ノチ工ス丿
こ! !フも… 決まっごる…
マイザ一…
Maiza...
It ought to have been impossible now to return to how things were on that ship...
ノチ工ス丿
も う あの痰穿ノごは…
戻カな! !はず左っ庭のノご…
I wanted to meet you!
会いたかつた…
会いたかつたよ
マイザ一一
I wanted to meet you so badly, Maiza!
うう… うつ うっ…
Yes, yes!
Firo.
フイ一口…
Mr. Maiza.
マイザ一さん…
俺 全部 分かつてます
I understand everything.
Firo, then I won't have to tell you...
フイ一ロ… それなら
言うまでもないでしよう…
Of all people, I gave it to you...
よりによつて あなた方に…
どうしだんですか? マイザ一さん
What's wrong, Mr. Maiza?
The harshness of having to live for eternity, to you people...
永遠に生きるという苦しみを
あなた方に…
What are you saying, Mr. Maiza?!
何言つてるんですか
マイザ一さん!
俺ら 全然気に してないですよ !
We don't mind it one bit!
On the contrary, we're glad we won't die!
むしろ死なないでいいんだ
ヒヤッホウつて感じですよ!
I feel like going "yahoo!"
I don't really understand, but "yahoo"!
よく分からんけど
ヒヤツホウ!
Yahoo! Cheer up, Maiza!
元気出せよ マイ ザ一
ハハハ… ヒヤツホウ!
頭領やヤグルマさんなんて 黙つてりゃ
長生きですねで ごまかせますよ!
Chief, and Mr. Yagmal too, if you keep your mouths shut, you could just pass yourselves off as long-lived without difficulty!
何を言うか フイ一口 !
What are you saying, Firo?!
新だなる幹部の誕生を祝つて
Celebrating the institution of our new executive, cheers!
乾杯!
Cheers!
乾杯 !
ささささ どうぞ どうぞ
Don't be shy. Here you go.
どうぞ
Here you go.
Here you go!
こんなめでたい席に
誘つてくれたんだからな!
It's such an honor to be invited to such a festive occasion!
So, we have to at least show our gratitude.
せめてもの お礼だね !
グレツ卜…
これでいいんだろうか…
Gerd...
Is it all right like this?
ノ位二 一丿
気 フ乙 ! ご〔 !庭ん左ヵ
結局 俺は止めなか フだ
So he noticed...
In the end, I didn't stop him.
We'll be able to get along for a long time, or so I thought anyway.
俺だちなら長続す する…
何となく
そう,雷っ庭だソプなんだヵ濃…
ノ位二一丿 まあ く !‥
But all right...
I'm waiting for you in Manhattan.
ノシヤ一ネ丿
マンノ!ッ夕ンさ痔ちます
フま誓も あなだき僧ちます
I will forever wait for you.
Please, please come and find me.
どうヵ…
どうヵ搜レ ご下さ! )
I will also try to find you.
私もぁなだき搜レます…
マンハツ夕ンと言われても
範囲が広すぎるなァ…
Writing just Manhattan... That's a little too large of a region, I think...
I didn't tell her my name either...
それに俺の名前も教えてないし…
Well...
まぁ ガンド一ルの兄弟に
義理を果たしたあとになる力ヾ…
It'll have to wait until I've fulfilled my obligations to the Gandors, but...
I will find you. Definitely.
捜してやるさ 必ずな
オロオロ… ウオツチ !
With this, we will have saved loads of children!
これで たくさんの子供たちが
救われたぞ 三リア!
Because those signals are poison, right, Isaac?!
毒電波からだね アイザツク !
Yeah! According to the English Sun and Nature or something,
ああ イギリスのサンだか
ネイチヤ一だかによると
conversations decreased amongst families because of mobile phones,
ケ一夕イの電波のせいで
家族から会話が失われ
children are only playing games, fathers get mistresses, and mothers have to work.
子供はグ一ムに走り
父親は外に愛人を作って
母親は働きに出るんだそうだ
家庭崩壊だね !
It's the collapse of the family!
ああ! だから俺たちが
それを食い止めるのさ!
Yeah! That's why we're stopping that!
少子化対策だね !
A plan against the decrease in child births!
By the way, Miria...
ところで三リア…
なあに? アイザツクう
What, Isaac?
I have this feeling that we haven't aged at all...
俺たち 年取ってないような
気がするんだけど
気のせいか ?
Am I just imagining it?
わあ! 本当だよォォォ !
わああああ!
It's true!
三リア一!
Miria!
Isaac!
アイザツクう~~ !
ぐぁしつつ !
I don't know how this happened, but...
どうして こうなつたか
分かんないけど
Does this mean we've been born anew?!
俺たちはぁ 常に新しく
生まれ変わってるってことかぁ?
It's refreshing! Every day is a birthday!
リフレツシユだね!
毎巳が誕生巳だね!
Then, we have to celebrate!
じやあ お祝いしなきゃなぁ !
Let's call everyone and have a party each day!
みんなを呼んで
毎巳パ一テイ一だ !
Isaac! Happy birthday!
わあ アイザック!
誕生日おめでとうォォォ !